self pest control we do 230,000 this year this is our first year we would like to be at 10 million
dollars okay i'm 18 working at doing partnership with my buddy who owns the pest control company
or uh initially i made the decision to partner with him all right after coming here and talking
to as many people as i can just absorbing people are telling me that maybe it's not a bid park
ship do you have any equity in this business five percent okay if i bring two million revenue it
okay so five percent if you bring two million revenue right so you zero now and he has a
hundred percent and this has two hundred thousand dollars of revenue currently yeah so what stops
you from driving two million dollars of revenue to your own business i i don't really know what's
stopping me i guess nothing in order for a partnership to make sense long term this should
make sense for you too they got to have money you don't have they got to have skills you don't have
they got to have time you don't have or they got to have network or distribution you don't have
money time experience skill distribution if we're both the same then one of us is